Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1995 UE.4.1.6
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 6 Locals, 2.
  - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) General Outgoing Correspondence, February 28, 1941 - June 22, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Harry Sherman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Work Stoppage and Contract Negotiation, June 17, 1942; 1. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 1)
      - Sherman to UE Regarding International Representative, Contract Negotiations and Factionalism, July 3, 1942; 2. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 2)
      - Sherman Telegram to General Executive Board and UE Regarding Appeal Charges Trial Committee, March 22, 1944; 3. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 3)
      - William Tanney Telegram to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Contract Negotiations, May 30, 1943; 4. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 4)
      - Tanney Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Contract Negotiations, June 1, 1943; 5. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 5)
      - Tanney Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members and Negotiations, June 1, 1943; 6. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 6)
      - Tanney Telegram to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Negotiations, June 1, 1943; 7. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 7)
      - Tanney Telegram to Matles Regarding Contract Negotiations, June 1, 1943; 8. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 8)
      - Tanney Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members and Contract Negotiations, July 2, 1943; 9. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 9)
      - Tanney to Fitzgerald Regarding Contract Negotiation Representatives, July 16, 1943; 10. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 10)
      - Tanney to Leo Jandreau Regarding Contract Negotiation Rrepresentatives, August 11, 1943; 11. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 11)
      - Tanney to Emspak, August 17, 1943; 12. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 12)
      - Tanney Telegram to General Executive Board Regarding Equitable Meter Contract, September 13, 1943; 13. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 13)
      - Tanney to Emspak Regarding Staff Finance, November 29, 1943; 14. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 14)
      - Leo Turner to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Contract Negotiations, June 22, 1944; 15. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 15)
      - Charles Wallace to Matles Regarding Factionalism, February 28, 1941; 16. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 16)
      - James Westen to Matles Regarding Contract Negotiations, May 13, 1941; 17. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 17)
      - Memo to Matles Regarding Meter Shops, December 4, 1941; 18. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 18)
      - Local 615 Members to General Executive Board Regarding Contract and Local Status, undated; 19. (Box 9, Folder 32, Item 19)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Pittsburgh, PA., Correspondence, 1960 - 1965 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Pennsylvania Electric Coil Company Correspondence, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Finances, July 28, 1941 - December 13, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Newspapers, You Name It?, Meterite, and The Industrial Advises, July 18, 1942 - May 21, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Leaflets, June 1941 - September 1943 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - "'Are You a Win the War' Member of Local 615?", June 1941; 1. (Box 9, Folder 37, Item 1)
      - "Local 615 Membership Speaks", April 1943; 2. (Box 9, Folder 37, Item 2)
      - "News about Contract Negotiations", August 1943; 3. (Box 9, Folder 37, Item 3)
      - "News on Negotiations", September 3, 1943; 4. (Box 9, Folder 37, Item 4)
      - "615 Membership Should Know", September 7, 1943; 5. (Box 9, Folder 37, Item 5)
      - "International President Exposes Plot", September 10, 1943; 6. (Box 9, Folder 37, Item 6)
      - "The UERMWA Stand by You at All Times!", September 1943; 7. (Box 9, Folder 37, Item 7)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Pamphlets, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - The Full Story of What Has Been Done for Local 615!, 1945; 1. (Box 9, Folder 38, Item 1)
      - A Society of Free Men, by Most Reverend Bernard J. Sheil, 1945; 2. (Box 9, Folder 38, Item 2)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Pittsburgh Mine Safety Appliance Company, April 29 - May 27, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Edwin Beal Letter to Louis Willer with Newsclipping, May 19, 1942; 1. (Box 9, Folder 39, Item 1)
      - Beal Letter to Fred Haug with April 29, 1942, Willer Letter to Beal and Questionnaire, May 19, 1942; 2. (Box 9, Folder 39, Item 2)
      - Haug Letter to Beal, May 21, 1942; 3. (Box 9, Folder 39, Item 3)
      - Willer Letter to Beal, May 21, 1942; 4. (Box 9, Folder 39, Item 4)
      - Willer Telephone Message to Beal, May 27, 1942; 5. (Box 9, Folder 39, Item 5)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Discussion with Representatives of Local 615 Regarding International-Local Relationship (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Equitable Meter Campaign Memoranda, February 24 - May 5, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Correspondence, March 31 - April 14, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Michael Fitzpatrick Letter to National Labor Relations Board Regarding Local 615 Equitable Meter Strike, March 31, 1944; 1. (Box 9, Folder 42, Item 1)
      - Leo Turner Memo to David Scribner Regarding Wisconsin Compensation Rating Bureau, April 14, 1944; 2. (Box 9, Folder 42, Item 2)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Correspondence, 1974 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Local 615 (Equitable Meter Company) Strikes, Monies, and Other Subsidies, 1979 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Local 616
    - Local 616 Contract, May 9, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Local 616 Officers Lists, April 1943 - March 4, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Local 616 General Incoming Correspondence, October 14, 1940 - July 2, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Julius Emspak to Malcolm Will Regarding Finances, October 14, 1940; 1. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 1)
      - Emspak to John Wahner Regarding Finances, October 22, 1940; 2. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 2)
      - Emspak to John Wagner Regarding Mailing List, November 8, 1940; 3. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Daniel Honard Regarding Local 616 Constitution, September 15, 1941; 4. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Honard Regarding Finances with June 15, 1942, Albert Olson Letter to Emspak, June 25, 1942; 5. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Frank Bednarowicz Regarding Local 616 Officers, June 3, 1943; 6. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Will Regarding Finances with July 27, 1944, Olson Letter to Frederick Livingston, July 31, 1944; 7. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Will Regarding Finances, October 3, 1944; 8. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 8)
      - Emspak to Bednarowicz Regarding Finances with Ray Klausner Letter to Olson, October 16, 1944; 9. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 9)
      - Emspak to John Angelotti Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 2, 1945; 10. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 10)
      - James Matles Telegram to Honard, May 2, 1941; 11. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 11)
      - Secretary to Matles to Honard Regarding Local 616 Jarecki Manufacturing Collective Bargaining with Memo, March 5, 1942; 12. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 12)
      - Matles to Honard Regarding Local 616 Jarecki Manufacturing Collective Bargaining and Staff Members, April 9, 1942; 13. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 13)
      - Matles to Fred Kaeberlein Regarding Local 616 Jarecki Manufacturing Collective Bargaining and Staff Members, April 14, 1942; 14. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 14)
      - Matles to Honard Regarding Factionalism and Staff Members, April 15, 1942; 15. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 15)
      - Norma Gould, Secretary to Matles, to Honard, June 16, 1942; 16. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 16)
      - Olson Letter to John Angelotti Regarding Finances, February 21, 1945; 17. (Box 9, Folder 47, Item 17)
    - Local 616 General Outgoing Correspondence, October 15, 1940 - July 28, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - John Angelotti to UE Regarding Finances, July 28, 1945; 1. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 1)
      - Frank Bednarowicz to UE Regarding Executive Order 9240 with Bednarowicz Letter to James Byrnes, April 28, 1943; 2. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 2)
      - Bednarowicz to UE Regarding Change of Address, May 30, 1943; 3. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 3)
      - Bednarowicz to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Membership with August 22, 1944, Emspak Letter to Michael Fitzpatrick, August 14, 1944; 4. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 4)
      - Bednarowicz to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 13, 1944; 5. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 5)
      - Dan Honard Telegram to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, May 1, 1941; 6. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 6)
      - Honard to UE Regarding Local 616 Constitution, September 1941; 7. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 7)
      - Honard to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Local 616 Jarecki Collective Bargaining and Contract, March 3, 1942; 8. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 8)
      - Honard to UE Regarding Change of Address, April 3, 1942; 9. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 9)
      - Honard to UE Regarding Local 616 Jarecki Collective Bargaining and Staff Members, April 5, 1942; 10. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 10)
      - Honard to UE Regarding Local 616 Jarecki Collective Bargaining and Staff Members, April 14, 1942; 11. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 11)
      - Honard to UE Regarding Local 616 Officers, April 29, 1942; 12. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 12)
      - Honard to Matles Regarding Factionalism and Local 616 Jarecki Collective Bargaining, June 10, 1942; 13. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 13)
      - Fred Kaeberlein to Matles Regarding Local 616 Jarecki Collective Bargaining, March 1941; 14. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 14)
      - Kaeberlein to Matles Regarding Local 616 Jarecki Collective Bargaining and Factionalism, April 1941; 15. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 15)
      - Anthony Krasinski to UE Regarding Local 616 Officers, July 1942; 16. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 16)
      - John Wagner to UE Regarding Finances, October 15, 1940; 17. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 17)
      - Wagner to UE Regarding Mailing List and Employment, October 17, 1940; 18. (Box 9, Folder 48, Item 18)
    - Local 616 Finances, Bonding and Malcolm Will Expense Letter, March 27 - September 19, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Local 616 Bonding, September 12, 1944 - January 14, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Allan McNeil to Julius Emspak, September 12, 1944; 1. (Box 9, Folder 50, Item 1)
      - Albert Olson to Ray Klausner, January 17, 1945; 2. (Box 9, Folder 50, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Walter Mugford, February 1, 1945; 3. (Box 9, Folder 50, Item 3)
      - Mugford to Emspak, February 26, 1945; 4. (Box 9, Folder 50, Item 4)
      - Klausner to Mugford, March 5, 1945; 5. (Box 9, Folder 50, Item 5)
      - Olson to Stephen Rosner, December 6, 1945; 6. (Box 9, Folder 50, Item 6)
      - Rosner to David Scribner, December 20, 1945; 7. (Box 9, Folder 50, Item 7)
      - Scribner to Rosner, January 14, 1946; 8. (Box 9, Folder 50, Item 8)
    - Local 616 Albert Smith to James Matles Regarding Local 616 Jarecki Collective Bargaining and Staff Members, April 15, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Local 616 (Formerly Members of Local 623), 1963 - 1978 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Local 616 Agreements with Pittsburgh Commercial Heat Treating Company, 1978 - 1986 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Local 616 Agreements with Pittsburgh Commercial Heat Treating Company, 1985 - 1986 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Local 617
    - Local 617 Proposed Constitutional Amendment, September 11, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Local 617 Officers Lists, June 9, 1944 - November 25, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Local 617 General Incoming Correspondence, September 26, 1940 - February 2, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Harold Briney to Mary Murphy Regarding Finances, November 24, 1942; 1. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 1)
      - William Cahn to Jack Mylott Regarding Publicity, February 20, 1946; 2. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 2)
      - Julius Emspak to Murphy Regarding Mailing List, September 26, 1940; 3. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Mailing List, October 17, 1940; 4. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Mailing List, November 8, 1940; 5. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 6. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Finances, January 2, 1941; 7. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 7)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Finances, February 4, 1941; 8. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 8)
      - Emspak to Frank Bolt Regarding UE News, February 27, 1941; 9. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 9)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Finances, March 3, 1941; 10. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 10)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Finances, April 2, 1941; 11. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 11)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Finances, May 12, 1941; 12. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 12)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Mailing List, January 12, 1942; 13. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 13)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Finances, March 26, 1942; 14. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 14)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding UE News, July 23, 1942; 15. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 15)
      - Emspak to Murphy Regarding Change of Address, January 19, 1943; 16. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 16)
      - Norma Gould, Secretary to Emspak, May 3, 1944; 17. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 17)
      - Emspak to James Conroy Regarding Finances, May 4, 1944; 18. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 18)
      - Emspak to Leonard Stegailor Regarding Veterans Finances, January 23, 1945; 19. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 19)
      - Emspak to John Logan Regarding Local 617 Dues Officers, May 3, 1945; 20. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 20)
      - Emspak to Logan Regarding Dues Check-Off and Finances, October 15, 1946; 21. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 21)
      - Emspak to Thomas Flanagan Regarding Local 617 Strike and Finances, October 31, 1946; 22. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 22)
      - Emspak to Logan Regarding Per Capita Tax, January 9, 1947; 23. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 23)
      - Emspak to Logan Regarding Finances, February 2, 1947; 24. (Box 9, Folder 57, Item 24)
    - Local 617 General Incoming Correspondence, May 14, 1941 - October 16, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Julius Emspak to Albert Nagn Regarding Political Action Committee, March 5, 1947; 1. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 1)
      - Emspak to Thomas Flanagan Regarding Finances, April 2, 1948; 2. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 2)
      - Emspak to Flanagan Regarding Westinghouse Organization and Meadville, May 25, 1948; 3. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 3)
      - Emspak to Flanagan Regarding Wages and Finances, September 23, 1948; 4. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 4)
      - Emspak to Frank Whaler Regarding Finances, January 23, 1950; 5. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 5)
      - Emspak to Whaler Regarding Finances, April 3, 1950; 6. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 6)
      - Emspak to Whaler Regarding Finances, April 18, 1950; 7. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 7)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Local 617 Regarding Local 617 Constitution, December 29, 1942; 8. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 8)
      - Michael Fitzpatrick to Bernard Barry Regarding Finances and Sharon Westinghouse Organization, December 9, 1941; 9. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 9)
      - Nathan Gellar to Mary Murphy Regarding Finances, July 8, 1941; 10. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 10)
      - James Matles to Henry Donlaies Regarding Staff Members, May 14, 1941; 11. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 11)
      - Matles to J. M. Miller Regarding Sharon Westinghouse Organization, May 1, 1942; 12. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 12)
      - Matles to Robert Cardwell Regarding Publicity, March 3, 1947; 13. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 13)
      - Matles Telegram to Flanagan, May 27, 1947; 14. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 14)
      - Matles to Whaler Regarding Staff Members, December 3, 1948; 15. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 15)
      - Matles to Murphy Regarding Sharon Westinghouse, October 16, 1957; 16. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 16)
      - Edward Matthews Telegram to Leornard Stegailov Regarding Bridgeport GE Organization and White Collar Workers, August 31, 1945; 17. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 17)
      - Charles Newell to John Logan Regarding Finances and Per Capita Tax, October 30, 1946; 18. (Box 9, Folder 58, Item 18)
    - Local 617 General Outgoing Correspondence, May 4, 1941 - October 5, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - J. Conroy Telegram to Edward Mathews Regarding Finances, May 4, 1944; 1. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 1)
      - Henry Donalies to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 4, 1941; 2. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 2)
      - Donalies to Julius Emspak Regarding Salaried Workers, March 29, 1945; 3. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 3)
      - Donalies to UE Regarding Factionalism and Membership, October 1, 1945; 4. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 4)
      - Thomas Flanagan to Thomas Wright Regarding Officers and Anti-Labor Legislation, May 2, 1947; 5. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 5)
      - Flanagan to Wright Regarding Conscription, June 21, 1946; 6. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 6)
      - Flanagan to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 14, 1947; 7. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 7)
      - Flanagan Memo to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 17, 1947; 8. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 8)
      - Flanagan Telegram to Seymour Linfield Regarding Veterans, March 5, 1947; 9. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 9)
      - Flanagan Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Taft-Hartley Bill and Rally, May 26, 1947; 10. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 10)
      - Flanagan Memo to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 9, 1947; 11. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 11)
      - Flanagan Telegram to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 5, 1948; 12. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 12)
      - Flanagan Memo to Emspak Regarding Meadville and Organization, March 22, 1948; 13. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 13)
      - Flanagan to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 17, 1948; 14. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 14)
      - Flanagan Telegram to Matles Regarding Factionalism and Stewards Council, November 18, 1949; 15. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 15)
      - Guy Fragle Telegram to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Negotiation Board, October 4, 1949; 16. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 16)
      - Fragle Telegram to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Negotiation Board, October 5, 1949; 17. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 17)
      - T. J. Gorman Telegram to Matles, August 2, 1941; 18. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 18)
      - Harold Jamieson Memo to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, June 30, 1947; 19. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 19)
      - Jamieson Memo to Emspak Regarding Packinghouse Workers Strike and Fund, February 3, 1949; 20. (Box 9, Folder 59, Item 20)
    - Local 617 General Outgoing Correspondence, November 13, 1940 - October 6, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - John Logan to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 15, 1944; 1. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 1)
      - Logan to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, March 9, 1945; 2. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 2)
      - Logan to Emspak Regarding Staff Member and Finances, April 26, 1945; 3. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 3)
      - Logan to Emspak Regarding SWEA at Sharon Westinghouse and Staff Finances, September 19, 1945; 4. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 4)
      - Logan to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 2, 1946; 5. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 5)
      - Logan to David Scribner Regarding Staff Finances, August 12, 1946; 6. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 6)
      - Logan to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with October 15, 1946, Emspak Letter to Charles Newell, October 4, 1946; 7. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 7)
      - Logan to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 8, 1946; 8. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 8)
      - Logan to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with January 9, 1947, Emspak Letter to Fitzpatrick, January 2, 1947; 9. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 9)
      - Logan to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 22, 1947; 10. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 10)
      - Emma Mae Telegram to James Matles Regarding Westinghouse Negotiating Board, October 6, 1949; 11. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 11)
      - Ed Matthews to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Organizations, November 30, 1948; 12. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 12)
      - J. M. Miller to Matles Regarding Sharon Organization, April 17, 1942; 13. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 13)
      - Mary Murphy to UE Regarding Westinghouse Conference and Wages, November 13, 1940; 14. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 14)
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Westinghouse and Wages, December 2, 1940; 15. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 15)
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Officers, April 24, 1941; 16. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 16)
      - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Officers, December 15, 1941; 17. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 17)
      - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, December 29, 1941; 18. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 18)
      - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, March 15, 1942; 19. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 19)
      - Murphy to Emspak Regarding Publicity, July 8, 1942; 20. (Box 9, Folder 60, Item 20)
    - Local 617 General Outgoing Correspondence, January 26, 1941 - October 28, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Mary Murphy to James Matles Regarding Wage Grievance with Local 617 Letter to John Steelman, Deptartment of Labor, August 17, 1942; 1. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 1)
      - Murphy to Julius Emspak Regarding Office Supplies, January 28, 1943; 2. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 2)
      - Murphy to Editor of UE News Regarding Publicity and Sharon Election, September 7, 1957; 3. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 3)
      - Murphy to Matles Regarding Staff Finances and Mailing List, October 28, 1957; 4. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 4)
      - Jack Mylatt to Edward Matthews Regarding Publicity and Wages, January 29, 1946; 5. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 5)
      - Albert Nagy to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, February 26, 1947; 6. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 6)
      - Nagy to Emspak Regarding PAC, April 16, 1947; 7. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 7)
      - Madge Rudich to UE Regarding Anniversary Dance with Ticket, March 2, 1945; 8. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 8)
      - Thomas Songer to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 1, 1950; 9. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 9)
      - Leonard Stegailov to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Initiation Stamps, January 19, 1945; 10. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 10)
      - Stegailov to R. L. Rodgers Regarding Poll Tax Legislation and Fair Employment Practices Bill, June 1945; 11. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 11)
      - Stegailov to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 21, 1949; 12. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 12)
      - Stegailov to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and ACTU-Carey-Block Group, March 17, 1949; 13. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 13)
      - Stegailov to Local 617 Regarding Clothing Project, Wages and Taft-Hartley Act, undated; 14. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 14)
      - Frank Whalen to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 4, 1950; 15. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 15)
      - Whalen to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members, East Pittsburgh and Sharon Organization, December 20, 1950; 16. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 16)
      - Whalen to Emspak Regarding IUE Inter-Union Rivalry and Staff Finances, August 20, 1951; 17. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 17)
      - Mary Whitehead to UE News Regarding Mailing List, June 18, 1951; 18. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 18)
      - Sophie Memo to Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 6, 1945; 19. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 19)
      - Local 617 Executive Board to UE Regarding Westinghouse Conference and National Agreement, January 26, 1941; 20. (Box 9, Folder 61, Item 20)
    - Local 617 Finances, Salary and Expense Letters, July 28, 1941 - May 11, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Local 617 Shipment Notices, Receipts, Financial Report, January 24, 1950 - November 1957 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Local 617 Newspaper, Sharon News, February 4, 1942 - August 10, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 64-65)
    - Local 617 Newspaper Clippings, July 18 - December 15, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - "Westinghouse Employees OK Defense Aid", July 18, 1941; 1. (Box 9, Folder 66, Item 1)